# DÁLCIO GARCIA

Luanda, Angola · +244 935 427 504

dalciomacuetegarcia@gmail.com · LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/dalcio-garcia Portfolio: https://dalciogarcia.vercel.app/ · GitHub: https://github.com/dalcio

Passionate Web and Mobile Developer with 1+ years of experience. Excited to continually learn from others, growing more and more. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill set. Able to bring amazing product designs to life with testing and debugging processes. Proficient in a variety of technologies including JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJS, React and React Native, HTML3, CSS and more, including popular frameworks like Redux, NextJS, Styled Components, Styled System and others. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects as well as collaborate in a team environment.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

NOV, 2021 - JAN, 2022

#### WEB DEVELOPER, OKUSSAKULA

I created the landing page with ReactJS and Give Birth System with NextJS for Okussakula Startup consuming from backend API made with .Net Core.

MAR, 2021 - SEP, 2021

#### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER, ABASTEÇA STARTUP

I was responsible to develop the ecosystem of Abasteça Startup.

I created a website to manage Abasteça Services with Next Js.

I also created two applications, one related with geolocation and the was to manage the Abasteça subsystems using Expo.

All applications were integrated with firebase.

MAR, 2021 – JUL, 2021

### REACT NATIVE MOBILE DEVELOPER, BAT DEV

I was responsible for bringing a UI and UX design to life using Expo a framework and platform for universal React apps. I built an application that involves concepts such as delivery, e-commerce and much more. I also use TypeScript to build the app.

OCT, 2020 – MAR, 2021

## FRONT END MOBILE DEVELOPER, MOCHI NOIR

I was responsible to create a mobile application with React Native and Typescript. The application was based on delivery app using 3rd party libraries API and consuming a Restful API back-end. I also wrote unit tests.

#### **EDUCATION**

**MARCH 2017 - PRESENT** 

**GRADUATION, INSTITUTO SUPERIOR POLITÉCNICO DE TECNOLOGIAS E CIÊNCIAS** 

It's okay to brag about your GPA, awards, and honors. Feel free to summarize your coursework too.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- NodeJS
- ReactJS

- React Native & Expo
- TypeScript
- React Frameworks (Redux, NextJS, and others).

# **LANGUAGES**

PORTUGUESE NATIVE SPEAKER ENGLISH B2
FRENCH A1

## **HOBBIES**

I like to run a little every day of the week to free my mind and improve my creativity, I also love food and cooking and I like to meditate to improve my self-control.